Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Bureau of Administration
  - Subseries I.4: Personnel and Management Division. Country File
    - Classification (413) (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Financial and Account Operations, Survey of (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - History Plans (150) (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting, Staff (293) (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Overtime and Compensatory Leave (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Report, General (270) (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales (450) (Box BA/16, Folder Side 2)
  - Subseries I.5: Personnel Division. Subject File
    - Administration, Mission (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative Services (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement File, H.I.A.S.ter (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement Non-Paying Countries, H.I.A.S.ter (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Allowance, Living and Quarters, 1945 Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Appeals, Policy re: (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Appointments and Employee Record (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Appointment, Types of, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Appointments, W.A.E. (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Assignment and Responsibility within UNRRA Headquarters (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Assignments and Duties, Personnel Division (224.2) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Awards, Policy re: (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Biographical Sketches (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Biographical Sketches, Top Employees (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Bonus Plan (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Administrative, 1945 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget European Mission Reserve (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Personnel, Miscellaneous 1944 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Personnel Service, 31 Aug. 1945 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Personnel Service, March 1946 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Procedures (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Supplies (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Cable Procedure (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Chiefs and Deputy Chiefs of Missions (Suggested) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative and Secretary Positions (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Finance (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Relief (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Supplies (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Coal Mining Administration (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Communications Rehabilitation (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Department of Materials (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Highway Rehabilitation (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Industrial Department National Resources Commission (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Insurance (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Management Budget (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Medicine or Health (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Ministry of Agriculture and Forestry (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - National Animal Husbandry (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - National Conservancy Commission (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - National Forestry Research Bureau (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - National Pesticides and Sprayers Experimental Plant (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Observers (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Railway Repair and Rehabilitation (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Water Transport and Chinese Merchant Marine (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Classification, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Committees (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Boudreau (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Boudreau Committee Report (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Joint Committee of UN-UNRRA on Social Welfare (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Position Review Committee (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Training, Committee on (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Committees, Personnel (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Communications, Procedures (written) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Conference: The Bretton Woods (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Congress, Relations with (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Conscientious Objectors, Employment of (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Conscientious Objectors, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Country Missions - Budget (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Credit Union (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Decorations, Policy re: (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Director General, Office of (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Director of Personnel's Office (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons 1944 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons Operations, not dated (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons Program, January-March 1945 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons Program, April-December 1945 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Draft Deferments (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employee Counselor, Beecher (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employees, Classes of, Policy re: (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employees Compensation Plan, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employment of Japanese Americans, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employment of Nationals of Other Countries, Negroes?, Catholics, etc (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Employment Procedures (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Expense Ledgers (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Families to the Field, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Farm Security Administration, Release Clearance (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Fellowships, Miscellaneous (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Assignment Physical Examination, Procedure (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field, Delegation to (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Employees Returned to Headquarters, Policy Procedure (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Offices, Memos and Statistics (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Personnel Exclusive of London as of April 30, 1944 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Personnel, Returned (224/26) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Personnel Section, Returned (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Field Service Regulations, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance Division (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Form Letters (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Form Letters, Personnel Correspondence (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Headquarters Personnel by Organization Location as of April 30, 1944 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Headquarters Personnel by Salary Levels as of April 30, 1944 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Health Division (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Historian (224/10) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - History File (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Home Station, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Howell, William, Miscellaneous (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Immunities (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Insurance, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - International Children's Emergency Fund (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - IRQ File (International Refugee Organization) (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - IRQ - Recommendations for Staff Regulations (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Investigations Unit (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Job Description (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Joint Planning Commission (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Policy (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters- Conditional Carbon Copies (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters - General Carbon Copies (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters to and from Cramer (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters from W.F. Howell, February-April 1946 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters to Mr. Howell, February 1946 (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters to and from Katzin (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters from Field Offices to Menshikov (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Liaison - Miscellaneous (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Manual, Personnel (Box BA/17, Folder Side 2)
    - Manual, Personnel Management, 1 April 1945 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Meetings, Staff, Finance and Administration, Minutes of (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Meetings Minutes, Miscellaneous and Investigation (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Meetings, Personnel Division, Minutes and Agenda (with Corson) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Meetings, Senior Staff, Minutes and Agenda, Personnel and Training (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Memorandums (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Carbon Copies (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - for February 1946 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - to and from Corson (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - to and from Corson, September-December 1944 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - to and from Gill (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - to Hendrickson (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Office of Country Mission Affairs - Transfer of Personnel from Bureau of Areas (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization - Bureau of Areas (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization and Reports (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization, Employee (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement (224/27) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement Policy Procedure (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement Procedure (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel (Note: imperfect alphabetization) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Actions, Procedures (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Change of Status of (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Confidential Recruitment and Employment Status, June 1946, Vol. 1 (224) Correspondence, Miss Baynard (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Costs (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Division,Personnel - General and Organizational (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Headquarters Personnel, List of (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Loaned Personnel (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedures in the Field (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruited from Army by C.H. Cramer (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruited in Brazil and Australia (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel and Training - Civil Service Assembly (CSA), U.S. and Canada - Personnel and Training Division Membership (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Operating Program, January-June 1945 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel Transfer from OFRRO (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel Utilization (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Physical Exams (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Policy - Probationary Period (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Positions, Requests for P-39, February 1946 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Proposed Policies (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedure, Applicant Record (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedure, Standards of Selections (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedures (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedures 1945 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedures 1946 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Promotions, Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Provident Fund, Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Provident Fund - Coverage, Financial Aid (870) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Ratings, Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Recruiting Schedule, UNRRA-Canada (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Recruitment (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Recruitment (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - for Clothing Drive (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - of Catholics (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - of Chiefs of Mission (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - of Clergymen (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Headquarters (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Health (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - from Military (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Negroes (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Non-Americans (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Overseas Positions (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy (224/1) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy and Planning (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Requirements (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Schedules (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Sources (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Sources - Catholic Welfare Agencies (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Sources Educational (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Sources Governmental (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Sources Non-Governmental (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission, Consuls, Miscellaneous Panels (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Re-Employment Rights Reports (Note: imperfect alphabetization) (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Counselor's Monthly (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Pending Monthly (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Administration at Headquarters (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Missions - Statistical Report (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Interview Reports (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous Reports (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Action Summary Weekly (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Work Load Reports (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Requests - Commander R.G.A. Jackson (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Resignations, Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Rundown Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - 1944 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - 1945 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - 1946 and 1947 (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Automatic Increases (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Selective Service, Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Social Security Board (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Space (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Staff (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Key, Headquarters (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Organization (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Relationships (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Turnover of (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Stateless and Ex-Enemy Nationals, Employment of Stateless, Recruit Policy (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Statistics, Staff, by Organizational Unit (Box BA/18, Folder Side 2)
    - Statistics and Reports (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Tabulations, Daily, for February 1946 (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Taxes (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Taxes, Refund of Withholding (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Telex (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Telex Conversations (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Telex Conversations (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Termination Policy (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Termination Reports, May 1946 (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Terminations, Policy (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Terminations, Statistics (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Training (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Training (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Training School (not Training Reports) (224/20) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Transportation, Field, Schedules (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Travel Authorization (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Travel, Indirect, Rules Regarding, for Returnees (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Trip - Harris (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Trip - Munk (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Trips, Field (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Trips, Recruiting (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Uniforms, Policy on (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - United Nations Personnel (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Personnel Policy (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Salary and Wage Coordination Committee (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - "Unrralated Facts" - Complete File (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Staff Society (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Staff Society (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Grievance Committee (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Meetings (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization Bulletins (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Overseas (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Recreation Committee, Thad Martin (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Vacancies, Headquarters Personnel as of April 30, 1944 Voluntary Agencies (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Welfare Division (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Who's Who Appendix (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Wives, Policy (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Workmen's Compensation Plan (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
  - Subseries I.6: Personnel Divison. Country File
    - Albania Mission - Reports, Force Reports (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Albanian Mission (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Australian Mission - Personnel Flow Chart (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Australian Recruitment (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Austrian Mission (Box BA/19, Folder Side 1)
    - Balkan Mission (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Establishment of, File No. 1, to September 1944 (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Establishment of, File No. 2, from October 1944 on (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Functional Statements (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous Belgium Mission Brazil - Braga Byelorussia and. Ukraine (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Canadian Correspondence (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Canadian Recruitment (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Areas and Operations, Accounting and Finance (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget and Positions, Vol. I, through February 1946 (224/7) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget and Positions, Vol. II, February-June 1946 (224/7) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget and Positions, Vol. III, July-September 1946 (224/7) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget and Positions, Vol. IV, October 1946 on (224/7) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - CNRRA, Jobs (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - CTP, Control Records (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Directors, Regional (024/7) (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance Contributions (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Job Descriptions (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Material - Miscellaneous (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Material - Miscellaneous (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box BA/19, Folder Side 2)
    - China Mission (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - 1944, Miscellaneous (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945, January-August (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945, September 1 - December 31 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - China Office (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel, October 1944-December 1945, Vol. I (224/12) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel, January 1946, Vol. II (224/12) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel Needs (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel, Welfare (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Promotions (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - China (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization Data, Early (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel, Agrehab (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment 1944 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment 1947 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment and Employment Status (224) - EOD (entered on duty) Lists, December 1945, Vol. I (224/12) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment and Employment Status (224) - Shops Program, April 1946, Vol. I (224/23) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment and Employment Status (224) - Returned Field Personnel, December 1947, Vol. I (224/26/4) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment and Employment Status (224) - Termination, July 1946 to May 1947, Vol. I (224/25) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment and Employment Status (224) - Termination, June 1947 to April 1948, Vol. II (224/25) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment Needs for China (old) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruitment Status, Vol. I, through 31 May 1946 (224/9) Recruitment Status, Vol. II, from 1 June 1946 on (224/9) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Report (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Surprop Office - Manila (224/29) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Training (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Vacancies (224/8) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Denmark, Liaison (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Denmark Mission Report Narrative (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - European Missions, Establishment of, No. 1 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - European Missions, Establishment of, No. 2 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - European Regional Office (ERO) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget Control Committee (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 3rd quarter 1946 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Department List, 1 January 1945 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Forms, Personnel and Staff Regulations (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters to ERO (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting, Administrative Council (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting, Heads of Divisions (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Notes for the Week and Miscellaneous (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - P.D.M.I.'s (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel in ERO as of 30 April 1944 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Instructions (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Recruitment (224/18) (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Report, Progress (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Staff List, Grades and Salary Organizational Units (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Telephone Calls to London, Weekly (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - European Regional Office and Field (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Staff Regulations Compensation Plan (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Statistics, Personnel (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - European Regional Office and Missions Charts (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Far Eastern Mission (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Finnish Recruitment, Current Finland Mission (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - French Mission (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - French, Recruitment of (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Operations (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Operations 1946 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Operations Budget (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Job Specifications (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Reorganization (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany Mission - Statistical Analysis Class I Employees 1945-46 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Greece Mission (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Country Mission General Regulations 1944 (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/20, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Holland Mission - Budget, Personnel Services (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Honolulu Office, Recruitment and Employment Status, October 1946, Vol. I (224/22) Hungarian Recruitment (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Indian Recruitment (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Indian Nationals, Recruitment of (224/11) (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Italy Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Biographical Sketches (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget, 3rd quarter (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Recruiting Schedules (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Korean Mission - Position (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Latin America - Alfaro Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Latin America - Santos Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Luxembourg Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Netherlands Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Norwegian Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippine Mission - P.I. Personnel (227/17) (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippines, Recruitment in P.I. (224/16) (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippeville Mission (Box BA/21, Folder Side 1)